{
    "id": "d1cff28308d64361957439fa4fcc9229",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Our garden looks awful this summer. There are too ……………. weeds.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t ………………. flowering plants in our garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "How ……………….. pages did you read?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "many",
                "much"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They say …………………. knowledge is a dangerous thing.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "the little"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am having ……………….. trouble passing my driving exam.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "lot of",
                "a lot of"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "...................... people can afford a home these days.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Little"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "You have ……………….. patience.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She earns ..................... money than I do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "fewer",
                "lesser"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "..................... of the information proved to be outdated.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Some",
                "Many"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t use ……………….. fertilizer last spring.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "most"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}